[
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Whistler%20was%20the%20codename%20of%20this%20Microsoft%20Operating%20System.",
        "correct_answer": "Windows%20XP",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Windows%202000",
            "Windows%207",
            "Windows%2095"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "When%20was%20the%20programming%20language%20%22C%23%22%20released%3F",
        "correct_answer": "2000",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "1998",
            "1999",
            "2001"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "On%20which%20computer%20hardware%20device%20is%20the%20BIOS%20chip%20located%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Motherboard",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Hard%20Disk%20Drive",
            "Central%20Processing%20Unit",
            "Graphics%20Processing%20Unit"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20languages%20is%20used%20as%20a%20scripting%20language%20in%20the%20Unity%203D%20game%20engine%3F",
        "correct_answer": "C%23",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Java",
            "C%2B%2B",
            "Objective-C"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "All%20of%20the%20following%20programs%20are%20classified%20as%20raster%20graphics%20editors%20EXCEPT%3A",
        "correct_answer": "Inkscape",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Paint.NET",
            "GIMP",
            "Adobe%20Photoshop"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The%20computer%20OEM%20manufacturer%20Clevo%2C%20known%20for%20its%20Sager%20notebook%20line%2C%20is%20based%20in%20which%20country%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Taiwan",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "United%20States",
            "Germany",
            "China%20%28People%27s%20Republic%20of%29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20was%20the%20first%20commerically%20available%20computer%20processor%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Intel%204004",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Intel%20486SX",
            "TMS%201000",
            "AMD%20AM386"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20was%20the%20name%20given%20to%20Android%204.3%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Jelly%20Bean",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Lollipop",
            "Nutella",
            "Froyo"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20the%20name%20for%20the%20failed%20key%20escrow%20device%20introduced%20by%20the%20National%20Security%20Agency%20in%201993%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Clipper%20Chip",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Enigma%20Machine",
            "Skipjack",
            "Nautilus"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20does%20the%20acronym%20CDN%20stand%20for%20in%20terms%20of%20networking%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Content%20Delivery%20Network",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Content%20Distribution%20Network",
            "Computational%20Data%20Network",
            "Compressed%20Data%20Network"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "How%20many%20cores%20does%20the%20Intel%20i7-6950X%20have%3F",
        "correct_answer": "10",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "12",
            "8",
            "4"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20one%20of%20these%20is%20not%20an%20official%20development%20name%20for%20a%20Ubuntu%20release%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Mystic%20Mansion",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Trusty%20Tahr",
            "Utopic%20Unicorn",
            "Wily%20Werewolf"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In%20the%20server%20hosting%20industry%20IaaS%20stands%20for...",
        "correct_answer": "Infrastructure%20as%20a%20Service",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Internet%20as%20a%20Service",
            "Internet%20and%20a%20Server",
            "Infrastructure%20as%20a%20Server"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20coding%20language%20was%20the%20%231%20programming%20language%20in%20terms%20of%20usage%20on%20GitHub%20in%202015%3F",
        "correct_answer": "JavaScript",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "C%23",
            "Python",
            "PHP"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20default%20theme%20that%20is%20installed%20with%20Windows%20XP%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Luna",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Neptune",
            "Whistler",
            "Bliss"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In%20the%20programming%20language%20%22Python%22%2C%20which%20of%20these%20statements%20would%20display%20the%20string%20%22Hello%20World%22%20correctly%3F",
        "correct_answer": "print%28%22Hello%20World%22%29",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "console.log%28%22Hello%20World%22%29",
            "echo%20%22Hello%20World%22",
            "printf%28%22Hello%20World%22%29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In%20HTML%2C%20which%20non-standard%20tag%20used%20to%20be%20be%20used%20to%20make%20elements%20scroll%20across%20the%20viewport%3F",
        "correct_answer": "%3Cmarquee%3E%3C%2Fmarquee%3E",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "%3Cscroll%3E%3C%2Fscroll%3E",
            "%3Cmove%3E%3C%2Fmove%3E",
            "%3Cslide%3E%3C%2Fslide%3E"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20correct%20term%20for%20the%20metal%20object%20in%20between%20the%20CPU%20and%20the%20CPU%20fan%20within%20a%20computer%20system%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Heat%20Sink",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "CPU%20Vent",
            "Temperature%20Decipator",
            "Heat%20Vent"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "How%20fast%20is%20USB%203.1%20Gen%202%20theoretically%3F",
        "correct_answer": "10%20Gb%2Fs",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "5%20Gb%2Fs",
            "8%20Gb%2Fs",
            "1%20Gb%2Fs"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20does%20%22LCD%22%20stand%20for%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Liquid%20Crystal%20Display",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Language%20Control%20Design",
            "Last%20Common%20Difference",
            "Long%20Continuous%20Design"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20operating%20system%20was%20released%20first%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Mac%20OS",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Windows",
            "Linux",
            "OS%2F2"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": ".at%20is%20the%20top-level%20domain%20for%20what%20country%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Austria",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Argentina",
            "Australia",
            "Angola"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20does%20the%20term%20GPU%20stand%20for%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Graphics%20Processing%20Unit",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Gaming%20Processor%20Unit",
            "Graphite%20Producing%20Unit",
            "Graphical%20Proprietary%20Unit"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20is%20the%20main%20CPU%20is%20the%20Sega%20Mega%20Drive%20%2F%20Sega%20Genesis%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Motorola%2068000",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Zilog%20Z80",
            "Yamaha%20YM2612",
            "Intel%208088"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20was%20the%20first%20Android%20version%20specifically%20optimized%20for%20tablets%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Honeycomb",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Eclair",
            "Froyo",
            "Marshmellow"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20of%20these%20people%20was%20NOT%20a%20founder%20of%20Apple%20Inc%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Jonathan%20Ive",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Steve%20Jobs",
            "Ronald%20Wayne",
            "Steve%20Wozniak"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "When%20did%20the%20online%20streaming%20service%20%22Mixer%22%20launch%3F",
        "correct_answer": "2016",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "2013",
            "2009",
            "2011"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What%20does%20the%20term%20MIME%20stand%20for%2C%20in%20regards%20to%20computing%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Multipurpose%20Internet%20Mail%20Extensions",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Mail%20Internet%20Mail%20Exchange",
            "Multipurpose%20Interleave%20Mail%20Exchange",
            "Mail%20Interleave%20Method%20Exchange"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which%20programming%20language%20was%20developed%20by%20Sun%20Microsystems%20in%201995%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Java",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Python",
            "Solaris%20OS",
            "C%2B%2B"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The%20name%20of%20technology%20company%20HP%20stands%20for%20what%3F",
        "correct_answer": "Hewlett-Packard",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Howard%20Packmann",
            "Husker-Pollosk",
            "Hellman-Pohl"
        ]
    }
]